A Guide to the Papers of Paul T. David
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Paul T. David
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
12793-c
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Contents List
- The Economics of Air Mail Transportation 1918-1936
  - Civil Service Bill Proposal 1936 (Box 1)
  - Proposal for a Service of General Administration of the National Government 1929 (Box 1)
  - Working Outline of Procedure for Study--Personnel 1936 (Box 1)
  - Comment on General Staff Memorandum 1936 (Box 1)
  - Personnel Administration and Public Administration 1936 (Box 1)
  - Parts I-III--Personnel Administration 1936 (Box 1)
  - Conference Notes of Different Groups 1936 (Box 1)
  - Supplementary Studies of Certain Phases of Personnel Administration 1936 (Box 1)
  - Staff Comments--First Mimeographed Editions 1936 (Box 1)
  - Outline--Memorandum on Personnel Administration 1936 (Box 1)
  - President's Committee Notes 1936 (Box 1)
  - Paul T. David--New York Conference 1936 May (Box 1)
  - Recommendations--Personnel Management 1936 (Box 1)
  - Part I--Introductory Statement on Personnel Management 1936 (Box 1)
  - Parts I-III--Personnel Administration 1936 (Box 1)
  - Part III--Recommendations on Personnel Administration 1936 (Box 1)
  - Conferences--Agricultural Department, etc. 1936 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Working Papers 1936 (Box 2)
  - Outline for New York Conference [n.d.] (Box 2)
  - Reorganization of the Government Agencies 1937 (Box 2)
  - Part V--Problems Related to the Extension of the Merit System [n.d.] (Box 2)
  - Reorganization Act of 1939 [n.d.] (Box 2)
  - Part II--Summary of Conclusions and Recommendations [n.d.] (Box 2)
  - Part I--The Problem of Effective Personnel Administration [n.d.] (Box 2)
  - Part III--Federal Personnel Administration As It Now Exists 1936 (Box 2)
  - Part IV--The Development of a Service of Personnel Administration 1936 (Box 2)
  - Civil Service Commission 1938 (Box 2)
  - Parts I-V n.d. (Box 3)
  - Personnel Administration in the Federal Service 1936, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Part III Copy with Comments 1936 (Box 3)
  - Parts I, IV and V n.d. (Box 3)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 July (Box 3)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 August (Box 3)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 August, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 October, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 July (Box 4)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 July, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Personal and Confidential 1936 August (Box 5)
  - Air Express 1931 (Box 5)
  - Statistics--Air Mail Service 1928-1931 (Box 5)
  - Air Line Pilots 1932 (Box 5)
  - The National Aeronautic Magazine 1934 April (Box 5)
  - Aviation magazine 1932-1933, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Annual Report [n.d.] (Box 5)
  - Summary of Report of Postal Service Committee 1931 (Box 5)
  - Appropriations and Expenditures 1929-1931 (Box 5)
  - Colonel L.H. Brittin 1932-1933 (Box 6)
  - Chronology of Contract Air Mail Routes 1930 (Box 6)
  - Government Operation Articles 1933-1934 (Box 6)
  - Government Operation of Air Transport Article [n.d.] (Box 6)
  - The Truth About Pilots' Pay 1933 (Box 6)
  - Air Transportation Report--Working Papers [1935-1936] (Box 6)
  - --Final Manuscript [1935] (Box 6)
  - --Discarded Manuscript [n.d.] (Box 6)
  - Pilots 1932-1935 (Box 6)
  - Coolidge Committee [1931-1933] (Box 6)
  - FCOT Report Notes--Air Service 1931-1933 (Box 7)
  - Federal Coordinator of Transportation 1936 (Box 7)
  - Pennsylvania Airlines 1934 (Box 7)
  - Questionnaire--Companies Engaged in Air Operations 1933 (Box 7)
  - The Air Mail Situation [1934] (Box 7)
  - Aviation in National Defense and Transportation 1933-1934 (Box 7)
  - A History of Government Operation of Air Mail Service [n.d] (Box 7)
  - Chapter I 1918 (Box 7)
  - Chapter II 1918-1921 (Box 7)
  - Chapter III 1921-1926 (Box 7)
  - Chapter IV [n.d] (Box 7)
  - Chapter V 1926-1927 (Box 7)
  - Chapter VI 1928-1930 (Box 7)
  - Chapter VII 1930-1932 (Box 7)
  - Chapter VIII [n.d.] (Box 7)
  - Chapter IX [n.d.] (Box 7)
  - Chapter X [n.d.] (Box 7)
  - Unused Chapters [n.d.] (Box 7)
  - Operating Statistics 1931-1932 (Box 8)
  - The Wind Factor in Flight 1923 (Box 8)
  - Holding Companies 1931 (Box 8)
  - Air Mail Service Schedules 1930-1931 (Box 8)
  - Revenue Material 1930 (Box 8)
  - Performance--Government Operation Wealth and Maintenance [n.d.] (Box 8)
  - Letters--Statistics in Aviation 1931-1933 (Box 8)
  - Legislation 1932 (Box 8)
  - Air Mail--Post Office Appropriations [n.d.] (Box 8)
  - Correspondence--Journal of Land and Public Utility Economics 1930 (Box 8)
  - Air Law Review 1931 (Box 8)
  - Aviation--Miscellaneous Papers [n.d.] (Box 8)
  - Airway Article Material 1929-1930 (Box 8)
  - Economic Aspects of the Airplane [n.d.] (Box 8)
  - Thesis--U.S. Material 1931 (Box 8)
  - Air Mail Material 1930 (Box 8)
  - The Post Office and Air Transport--History and Economics of the United States Air Mail Service [n.d.], 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Statistical Analysis of Air Mail Routes [n.d.] (Box 9)
  - The Economics of Air Transportation [n.d.], 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Press Clipping-- The Economics of Air Mail Transportation1934 (Box 9)
  - The Economics of Air Transportation 1933-1934 (Box 9)
  - Congressional Record 1934 April (Box 9)
  - Bibliographical Notes and File Cards [n.d.] (Box 10)
  - Bibliographical Notes and File Cards [n.d.] (Box 11)